let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following is a server-side Java Script object?",
        answer: "A. Function",
        options: [
           "A. Function",
            "B. File",
            "C. File upload",
            "D. date"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression",
        answer: "D. immediate if",
        options: [
            "A. Alternative to if-else",
            "B. Switch statement",
            "C. If-then-else statement",
           "D. immediate if"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: " The 'function' and 'var' are known as?",
        answer: "A. Keywords",
        options: [
            "A. Keywords",
            "B. Data types",
            "C. Declaration statements",
            "D. Prototypes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:",
        answer: "D. Division by zero",
        options: [
            "A. Syntax error",
            "B. Missing of semicolons",
            "C. Missing of Bracket",
            "D. Division by zero"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: " Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
        answer: "A. valueOf()",
        options: [
            "A. valueOf()",
            "B. toString()",
            "C.toLocaleString()",
            "D. toPrecision()"
        ]
    },
   
        {
            numb: 6,
            question: "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:",
            answer: "C.Both are equal in the value and data type.",
            options: [
               "A.Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
               "B.Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
               "C.Both are equal in the value and data type.",
               "D.Both are not same at all."
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 7,
            question: "In JavaScript, what will be used for calling the function definition expression:",
            answer: "A. Function literal",
            options: [
                "A. Function literal",
                "B. Function prototype",
                "C. Function calling",
                "D. Function declaration"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 8,
            question: "Which of the following one is the property of the primary expression:",
            answer: "D.stand-alone expressions",
            options: [
                "A.Contains only keywords",
                "B.basic expressions containing all necessary functions",
                "C.contains variable references alone",
                "D.stand-alone expressions"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 9,
            question: "Which one of the following operator is used to check weather a specific property exists or not:",
            answer: "B.in",
            options: [
                "A. Exists",
                "B.in",
                "C. exist",
                "D.within"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 10,
            question: "Which one of the following is not a keyword:",
            answer: "D. use strict",
            options: [
                "A. if",
                "B. with",
                "C. debugger",
                "D. use strict"
            ]
        }

    
];
